It's not out of gratitude
It's because I want to treat you well
Mr. Fu, is this a confession
If you think so then it is
So casual
It's not casual
Just afraid you'll demand proof again
Heh
At the wedding banquet
Your fingers were trembling
You were so pale signing the statement
When Su Yurou brought out those old things
It's not like you didn't feel wronged
You just didn't let
those feelings make decisions for you
In my past life I found out too late that you helped me
Back then I trusted and chose the wrong people
And put up with things I shouldn't have
So in this life
When I saw you in the corner at the banquet I thought
At least this time I can't let you slip away
So you chose me
I admit I knew you would win
But when I chose you
you hadn't become anyone yet
It was just you as a person
Worth me choosing all over again
Su Mengyao
It's hard not to take you seriously when you say that
Then take it seriously